Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Campaign for U.S. Senate, 1991; XIV.
  - Issue Research, 8.
    - Research on Pennsylvania Issues, including Thornburgh's Gubernatorial Record
      - Thornburgh's position on the federal revenue sharing program, February 5, 1985 (Box 933, Folder 6)
      - Pennsylvania Cancer Control, Prevention and Research Advisory Board, 1984 (Box 933, Folder 7)
      - Bell of Pennsylvania state contract, 1984 (Box 933, Folder 8)
      - Pennsylvania Enterprise Zones publications, 1982-1983 (Box 933, Folder 9)
      - Conshohocken, PA as an Enterprise Zone, 1986 (Box 933, Folder 10)
      - Pennsylvania economic development reports, 1983-1987 (Box 933, Folder 11)
      - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA) and women, 1988 (Box 933, Folder 12)
      - National Governors Association (NGA) suggestions for health insurance plans for the unemployed, July-October, 1983 (Box 933, Folder 13)
      - Aid to basic education, comparison with other states, 1983-1985 (Box 933, Folder 14)
      - Aid to Philadelphia, PA, June 14, 1985 (Box 933, Folder 15)
      - Balanced Budget Amendment, 1985-1986 (Box 933, Folder 16)
      - Economic Development Committee (EDC) and CLIME reports, 1982-1986 (Box 933, Folder 17)
      - Creation of jobs during governorship, 1979-1987 (Box 933, Folder 18)
      - "Reducing the Cost of State Government: A Report on Cost Reduction to the Taxpayers of Pennsylvania", 1979-1986 (Box 933, Folder 19)
      - Awards presented to Thornburgh from agencies, groups and other associations, 1982-1988 (Box 933, Folder 20)
      - "Transforming Pennsylvania's Mental Retardation System: The Thornburgh Years", April, 1988 (Box 933, Folder 21)
      - Rebuilding the Pittsburgh Midfield International Airport, information and press kit, 1988-1991 (Box 933, Folder 22)
      - Philadelphia Shipyard, 1988-1991 (Box 933, Folder 23)
      - American Petroleum Institute issues, 1988-1991 (Box 933, Folder 24)
      - Notch babies issue, 1991 (Box 933, Folder 25)
      - Bethlehem Steel Corporation and the steel industry, 1981-1991 (Box 933, Folder 26)
      - R. P. Simmons, chairman of the board of Allegheny Ludlum Corporation, regarding trade laws and negotiations, 1991 (Box 933, Folder 27)
      - Pennsylvania Rural Electric Association (REA), regarding "60 Minutes" segment on the REA, October 28, 1991 (Box 933, Folder 28)
      - "Science, Technology and Congress: Analysis and Advice from the Congressional Support Agencies," a report from the Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology and Government, October, 1991 (Box 934, Folder 1)
      - "Governor's Annual Work Force Report", 1987 (Box 934, Folder 2)
      - Pennsylvania Department of Transportation (PennDOT) annual report, 1985-1986 (Box 934, Folder 3)
      - "Choices for Pennsylvanians: Final Summary", June, 1986 (Box 934, Folder 4)
      - "Pennsylvania's Economic Development and Community Conservation Strategy," budget and policy brief, 1984 (Box 934, Folder 5)
      - Ben Franklin Partnership Challenge Grant Program for Technological Innovation: 48 month Progress Report, March, 1983-February, 1987 (Box 934, Folder 6)
      - "The Economic Development Partnership Board, Committee on the Housing Industry briefing book", 1988 (Box 934, Folder 7)
      - "Economic Impact of the Philadelphia Naval Base and Shipyard on the Philadelphia Metropolitan Area," prepared by the Pennsylvania Economy League (PEL), October, 1990 (Box 934, Folder 8)
      - Thornburgh's record with the Pennsylvania Builders Association, 1979-1987 (Box 934, Folder 9)
      - Project VOTE! and Governor Thornburgh's attempt to bar voter registration drives inside state government offices, 1984-1986 (Box 934, Folder 10)
      - Community-based housing policy, March-August, 1981 (Box 934, Folder 11)
      - Long-term housing for the homeless, 1984 (Box 934, Folder 12)
      - White House and Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Cost Reduction Projects, 1980 (Box 934, Folder 13)
      - Implementation of selected Governor's Housing Task Force recommendations, September, 1983 (Box 934, Folder 14)
      - Pennsylvania Housing Finance Agency (PHFA) initiatives, 1985-1986 (Box 934, Folder 15)
      - ACIR Balanced Budget Amendment recommendations, June, 1987 (Box 934, Folder 16)
      - "The Three Mile Island (TMI) Experience: Ten Lessons in Emergency Management," Governor Thornburgh's address to Duke University, April 18, 1985 (Box 934, Folder 17)
      - Annual and monthly unemployment rate rankings, May 25, 1982 (Box 934, Folder 18)
      - Abortion and family planning, 1981-1991 (Box 934, Folder 19)
      - Federal and state Job Training Partnership Acts (JTPA) and Customized Job Training (CJT) programs, 1983-1991 (Box 934, Folder 20)
      - Rockwell International New Castle planned plant closing, November, 1991 (Box 934, Folder 21)
      - Dangerous Juvenile Offenders (DJO) strategy and legislation, 1985 (Box 934, Folder 22)
      - Testimony on Dangerous Juvenile Offenders (DJO) legislation, September, 1985 (Box 934, Folder 23)
      - Medicaid co-payments regulations and proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 934, Folder 24)
      - Idea for "Pennsylvania War on Drugs", December, 1982-April, 1984 (Box 935, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania crime statistics, 1981-1983 (Box 935, Folder 2)
      - House Democratic Caucus "Statement of Policy" and analysis, April-May, 1981 (Box 935, Folder 3)
      - Transportation block grant to Counties ("Paratransit Project"), June, 1982-January, 1983 (Box 935, Folder 4)
      - Possible state actions relating to asbestos, May 3, 1985 (Box 935, Folder 5)
      - Reducing high school sports injury in Pennsylvania, July, 1981 (Box 935, Folder 6)
      - Meeting with Department of Public Works (DPW) regarding community mental health/mental retardation (MH/MR) and budget needs, July, 1983 (Box 935, Folder 7)
      - Indigent care and health care cost containment, September, 1985-June, 1986 (Box 935, Folder 8)
      - National Study Group on State Medicaid Strategies, January 2, 1984 (Box 935, Folder 9)
      - United Services Agency (USA) transportation system, May, 1983 (Box 935, Folder 10)
      - Philadelphia: Past, Present and Future project, 1982 (Box 935, Folder 11)
      - "Demographic Trends: Past, Present and Future," a speech delivered to the Republican Governors' Association (RGA) by Vincent P. Barbara, Director of the U.S. Bureau of the Census, November-December, 1980 (Box 935, Folder 12)
      - "Legislative Update: An Update Report of the October 2, 1979 Legislative Message of Dick Thornburgh", September 17, 1980 (Box 935, Folder 13)
      - Business Council economic development proposal, April, 1984-April, 1986 (Box 935, Folder 14)
      - Democrat "PREPARE" initiative for job training, January-February, 1986 (Box 935, Folder 15)
      - Job training legislation, September-November, 1986 (Box 935, Folder 16)
      - Criteria for the use of the Sunny Day Fund, January-August, 1986 (Box 935, Folder 17)
      - Use of pension funds for venture capital, September 23, 1985 (Box 936, Folder 1)
      - Plant closing legislation and strategies, 1983-1986 (Box 936, Folder 2)
      - Business production opportunities in Pennsylvania extended to corporations, including Saturn, February, 1985 (Box 936, Folder 3)
      - Pennsylvania Securities Commission, August-September, 1982 (Box 936, Folder 4)
      - Criticisms of Belden Daniels' consultative work to states, 1982 (Box 936, Folder 5)
      - "Governing the States: Reflections of Duke University's Gubernatorial Fellows," Capital Ideas newsletter of the National Governors' Association (NGA), November 1, 1986 (Box 936, Folder 6)
      - Labor and Industry, Evaluation of the Joint Departments of Labor and Industry/Public Welfare/Education Initiative to Increase Service to Welfare Recipients, September 8, 1987 (Box 936, Folder 7)
      - Economic development in Pennsylvania, January-August, 1987 (Box 936, Folder 8)
      - "Report to the Allegheny Board of Commissioners for the Economic Revitalization of the Monongahela, Youghiogheny, and Turtle Creek Valleys," prepared by the Mon Valley Commission, February, 1987 (Box 936, Folder 9)
      - Clifford Jones, president of the Pennsylvania Chamber of Commerce, article and budget report, February, 1986 (Box 936, Folder 10)
      - Economic "scene" for service jobs, 1985-1986 (Box 936, Folder 11)
      - Comparison of Pennsylvania economy to that of other Northeast states, August, 1985-March, 1986 (Box 936, Folder 12)
      - "Road to Renaissance: Growth Industries for Pennsylvania," prepared by the Pennsylvania Chamber of Commerce, April-June, 1986 (Box 936, Folder 13)
      - Asbestos in schools, September 10, 1986 (Box 936, Folder 14)
      - Department of Health Maternal and Child Health (MCH) funds, 1985-1986 (Box 936, Folder 15)
      - Pennsylvania health services for children, 1983-1986 (Box 936, Folder 16)
      - Chronically ill children, studies and research, 1983-1985 (Box 936, Folder 17)
      - Analysis of personal care boarding homes (PCBHs), November-December, 1986 (Box 936, Folder 18)
      - S.B. 337, regarding personal care boarding homes (PCBHs), November-December, 1986 (Box 936, Folder 19)
      - "A Study of 1982 Transfers to Criminal Court in Pennsylvania," prepared by the Juvenile Court Judges Commission, April 17, 1984 (Box 936, Folder 20)
      - National Governors' Association (NGA) meetings regarding various issues, 1982-1983 (Box 936, Folder 21)
      - National Governors' Association (NGA) meetings regarding criminal justice, talking points for Governor Thornburgh, July 30, 1984 (Box 936, Folder 22)
      - NGA Committee on Criminal Justice and Public Protection, February 25, 1985 (Box 936, Folder 23)
      - "Charting a Course for Services to Serious Youthful Offenders: Initial Findings of a Survey of Judges, Chief Juvenile Probation Officers, and District Attorneys regarding Serious Youth Offenders in Pennsylvania, prepared by the Pennsylvania DPW, April 18-19, 1984 (Box 936, Folder 24)
      - Statistics on Dangerous Juvenile Offenders (DJOs), January-February, 1986 (Box 937, Folder 1)
      - Questions and answers regarding Governor Thornburgh's Proposal to Crack Down on Dangerous Juvenile Offenders (DJOs), and legislation S.B. 838, March-September, 1985 (Box 937, Folder 2)
      - Achievements and zingers! for Northwest Pennsylvania, 1981-1986 (Box 937, Folder 3)
      - Governor's appearances in Northwest Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 937, Folder 4)
      - State assistance to Philadelphia, PA, 1978-1982 (Box 937, Folder 5)
      - "Factors Influencing the Economic Development of Pennsylvania," prepared by Wharton Applied Research Center (ARC), September, 1979 (Box 937, Folder 6)
      - Pennsylvania's sensitivity to the business cycle, March 25, 1982 (Box 937, Folder 7)
      - Contracting of minority businesses, January, 1985 (Box 937, Folder 8)
      - "Select Comments on Public Planning and Actions to Revitalize the Northeast with Special Attention to the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania," by Pat Choate, ca. 1979 (Box 937, Folder 9)
      - "Choosing a Place to Grow: Business Location Decisions in the 1970s," by David Birch, January, 1981 (Box 937, Folder 10)
      - "Economic Development Programs in Three District States (Pennsylvania, Delaware and New Jersey): Three Approaches," by Eleanor Craig, Business Review, September-October, 1983 (Box 937, Folder 11)
      - "Human and Research Development Resources for Advanced Technology in Pennsylvania," by Robert Coy and the Pennsylvania MILRITE Council, ca. 1979 (Box 937, Folder 12)
      - "Silicon, Sensors and Software: Listening to Advanced Technology Enterprises in Pennsylvania," a report by the Pennsylvania MILRITE Council, July, 1983 (Box 937, Folder 13)
      - Inc. magazine's small business climate ratings, October, 1982 (Box 937, Folder 14)
      - Job training funds, July, 1981 (Box 937, Folder 15)
      - "Analysis of Worksharing Concept and Feasibility for Use in Pennsylvania," prepared by the Office of Policy Development (OPD), December 13, 1982 (Box 937, Folder 16)
      - Youth employment programs, 1980 (Box 937, Folder 17)
      - Summary of H.B. 402, Usury deregulation legislation, January-March, 1985 (Box 937, Folder 18)
      - Pennsylvania banks, state v. national chartering, May-June, 1984 (Box 937, Folder 19)
      - "Overcoming the Limits to Personnel Cutbacks: Lessons Learned in Pennsylvania," by Bob Wilburn, 1980 (Box 937, Folder 20)
      - Tax incentives to encourage technological innovation, 1980-1981 (Box 937, Folder 21)
      - Employment changes in Pennsylvania, January, 1981 (Box 937, Folder 22)
      - Foreign investment in Pennsylvania, March 26, 1982 (Box 937, Folder 23)
      - "Balloon" interest and principal repayment on PIDA loans, August 23, 1982 (Box 937, Folder 24)
      - Municipal Economic Development Agency (MEDA) bill, S.B. 664, H.B. 1751, S.B. 1151, 1983-1984 (Box 937, Folder 25)
      - "Economic Development in Pennsylvania," prepared by Council for Community Development for Senator James Lloyd, 1982 (Box 937, Folder 26)
      - Office of Policy Development (OPD) reports on various issues, including lead-based paint, Head Start program, rental assistance, and child day care, 1983-1986 (Box 938, Folder 1)
      - Securities market and legislation, 1986 (Box 938, Folder 2)
      - Low income and public assistance projects, 1983-1986 (Box 938, Folder 3)
      - "Final report of the Environment/Energy Transition Study Team" for Governor-elect Dick Thornburgh, 28-Dec-78 (Box 938, Folder 4)
      - Environment/Energy Transition Study Team, background materials, 28-Dec-78 (Box 938, Folder 5)
      - "Pennsylvania's Future: Issues and Choices, Volume 1," a report by the Pennsylvania State Planning Board, December, 1978 (Box 938, Folder 6)
      - "Pennsylvania's Future: Issues and Choices, Volume 2," a report by the Pennsylvania State Planning Board, December, 1978 (Box 938, Folder 7)
      - "A Land Policy Program for Pennsylvania: A Final Policy Report," prepared by the Office of State Planning and Development, March, 1978 (Box 938, Folder 8)
      - Pennsylvania State Civil Service Commission Biennial Report, 1984-1986 (Box 938, Folder 9)
      - "Management of Subsidized Day Care in Allegheny County: Report to the Pennsylvania Department of Public Works (DPW)", November 3, 1986 (Box 938, Folder 10)
      - CEO Venture Fund, proposal for the Ben Franklin Partnership Seed Capital Fund Program, November 25, 1986 (Box 938, Folder 11)
      - "Adolescent Pregnancy in Pennsylvania: Prevention and Care, Toward a Statewide Plan," by Lulu Mae Nix (includes other teenage pregnancy materials), 1985-1987 (Box 938, Folder 12)
      - "Program and Policy Options for the Chronically Unemployed," by Demetra Smith Nightingale, September 18, 1984 (Box 939, Folder 1)
      - "Strategies for Reducing Infant Mortality in Pennsylvania," by the Pennsylvania Department of Health and the Ad. Hoc. Infant Mortality Community, December 11, 1985 (Box 939, Folder 2)
      - "The Tide is Turning: A Progress Report on the Agenda for Excellence in Pennsylvania Public Schools," by the Department of Education, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 3)
      - "Work and Welfare," State Services Program Brief by the National Governors' Association (NGA), November, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 4)
      - "'Pennsylvania Vital Statistics, Annual Report, 1987," by the Department of Health, May, 1989 (Box 939, Folder 5)
      - "Pennsylvania Natality and Mortality Statistics," by the Department of Health and Health Data Center, July 1, 1978 (Box 939, Folder 6)
      - York 2000 Commission, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 7)
      - Governor-elect Thornburgh's address to the Pennsylvania Society, 1978 (Box 939, Folder 8)
      - Mental Health/Mental Retardation (MH/MR) payment and emergency hospital admissions, 1984 (Box 939, Folder 9)
      - Centralized intake and case management demonstration project, October, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 10)
      - "A Sunset Performance Audit of the State Civil Service Commission", November, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 11)
      - "Survey of State and Local Government Expenditures for Low Income Persons" and Pennsylvania's response, August-October, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 12)
      - Governor's Statewide Block Grant Advisory Committee, final report, December, 1983 (Box 939, Folder 13)
      - "A Republican Environmental Agenda," a lecture by Governor Thomas Kean, May 13, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 14)
      - "Policy Analysis Background Briefing Paper: Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act (OBRA), Long Term Effect on Pennsylvania's Aid to Families with Dependent Children (AFDC) Program", August 13, 1984 (Box 939, Folder 15)
      - "Feasibility of a Block Grant to Counties for Handicapped Persons in Pennsylvania," by Ed Geiger, undated (Box 939, Folder 16)
      - "Enhancing the Operational Efficiency of Pennsylvania's Securities Markets: The Revised Pennsylvania Securities Act (RPSA)", October 1, 1983 (Box 939, Folder 17)
      - Policy paper on distressed communities, January 27, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 18)
      - National Governors' Association (NGA) Transition Assistance Program for the end of the Thornburgh administration, October, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 19)
      - Bills awaiting Governor Thornburgh's signature, July-December, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 20)
      - Providing assistance to the homeless, July 24, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 21)
      - ACIR Fiscal Discipline Report, December 22, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 22)
      - "The Medical Assistance Hospital Protective Payment System," by the Department of Public Works (DPW), February, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 23)
      - "Annual Report to the Governor, 1984-1985, and Governor's Coordination of Special Services Plan, 1986-1988," by the State Job Training Coordinating Council, June, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 24)
      - "What's Ahead for Pennsylvania's Economy? A Report on a Conference of Pennsylvania's Economic Future", April 19, 1983 (Box 939, Folder 25)
      - "Demographic Trends and Human Service Choices for Pennsylvanians," by Gordon F. DeJong, 1983-1986 (Box 939, Folder 26)
      - Infant Mortality Conference, Princeton, NJ, August 15-16, 1985 (Box 939, Folder 27)
      - Reports on economic performance and education by the Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology and Government, September, 1991 (Box 939, Folder 28)
      - "In Search of Proper Balance," National Symposium on Civil Justice, April 30-May 1, 1986 (Box 939, Folder 29)
      - "Escape from the Underclass" study, July 20, 1984 (Box 940, Folder 1)
      - "Capital Markets and Competitive Decline," by Richard Ellsworth, reprinted from the Harvard Business Review, September-October, 1985 (Box 940, Folder 2)
      - Wenger, Michael of the Appalachian Regional Commission (ARC), prepared remarks to the National Governors' Association (NGA) Committee on Economic Development and Technological Innovation meeting, Hilton Head Island, SC, August 25, 1986 (Box 940, Folder 3)
      - County Boards of Assistance, Dauphin, Berks and Bedford Counties, PA, 1983-1985 (Box 940, Folder 4)
      - "Social Policy," by House Wednesday Group, November 13, 1985 (Box 940, Folder 5)
      - Report of Subcommittee on Economic Development Tools, October 22, 1985 (Box 940, Folder 6)
      - Materials on workforce and business from Edward Donley of Air Products and Chemicals, Inc., September 19, 1991 (Box 940, Folder 7)
      - "Enhancing the Operational Efficiency of Pennsylvania's Securities Markets: Reforming the Pennsylvania Securities Act," for the Senate Republican Caucus Policy Committee, February 1, 1986 (Box 940, Folder 8)
      - "Pension Funds and Economic Development: How Public and Private Pension Funds Can Contribute to the Pennsylvania Economy," by the Pennsylvania MILRITE Council, March, 1983 (Box 940, Folder 9)
      - Options and strategies for addressing plant closings in Pennsylvania, January, 1984 (Box 940, Folder 10)
      - Emergency Aid to Financially Distressed Communities, S.B. 1249 and S.B. 1143, 1985 (Box 940, Folder 11)
      - Early Warning System (EWS) for fiscal distress, proposals and legislation, January-November, 1986 (Box 940, Folder 12)
      - Securities law reform, 1979-1987 (Box 940, Folder 13-15)
      - Dangerous Juvenile Offenders (DJO) legislation, S.B. 838, 1985-1986 (Box 940, Folder 16)
      - Anti-drug efforts, August 1, 1986 (Box 940, Folder 17)
      - Victims of crime, May-June, 1986 (Box 940, Folder 18)
      - Criminal justice zingers!, 1986-1987 (Box 940, Folder 19)
      - State aid to counties, 1986 (Box 940, Folder 20)
      - Local government talking points, April-August, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 1)
      - Amendments to the Parole Act, 1983-1984 (Box 941, Folder 2)
      - Pennsylvania efforts on behalf of women, 1979-1987 (Box 941, Folder 3)
      - Analysis of the "Women's and Children's Budget", February 7, 1985 (Box 941, Folder 4)
      - Radon update, July 30, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 5)
      - Background on drug law enforcement in Pennsylvania, July, 1984 (Box 941, Folder 6)
      - "Elder Abuse Prevention," a report by the Task Force on Elderly Crime Prevention, June 7, 1983 (Box 941, Folder 7)
      - Goals of sentencing modification, 1979-1987 (Box 941, Folder 8)
      - Criminal justice expenditures, July 22, 1982 (Box 941, Folder 9)
      - Crime rate changes in Pennsylvania, March 18, 1982 (Box 941, Folder 10)
      - Impact of federal finances on Pennsylvania, 1984-1985 (Box 941, Folder 11)
      - Veterans and agriculture initiatives, July 17, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 12)
      - Assistance to urban areas, August 6, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 13)
      - "Pennsylvania Firsts," prepared by the Office of the Budget, undated (Box 941, Folder 14)
      - Utility statistics, May 19, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 15)
      - "Analysis of Allegheny County's Proposed Revisions in State Regulatory Mandates", 1979-1987 (Box 941, Folder 16)
      - Housing, September 8, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 17)
      - Voluntary repayment of advances from Federal Unemployment Compensation Loan Fund, May, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 18)
      - County expenditure reports, June-September, 1986 (Box 941, Folder 19)
      - Education and training assistance to District Attorneys, January-March, 1983 (Box 941, Folder 20)
      - Education program audits with corrections, June 26, 1980 (Box 941, Folder 21)
      - District Attorneys Commission, 1981-1983 (Box 941, Folder 22)
      - Gun control, 1973-1988 (Box 941, Folder 23)
      - Generalized Aptitude Test Battery for Selection and Referral in Employment and Training Programs, and the race norming issue, July, 1990-September, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 24)
      - Foreign aid, 1990-1991 (Box 941, Folder 25)
      - Pennsylvania's involvement in the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) and relations with Mexico, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 26)
      - "Economic Blueprint for Pennsylvania," Pennsylvania Senate Republican initiative, February-July, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 27)
      - Walt Plosila's ideas for economic development in Pennsylvania, ca. 1985 (Box 941, Folder 28)
      - Duquesne Light Company, power plant reactivation and transmission line initiative to spend new capital investments, August 28, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 29)
      - Pittsburgh's Dropout Prevention program, September 23, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 30)
      - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) and impact in Pennsylvania, September, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 31)
      - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Pittsburgh district, proposed corps reorganization study, September 6, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 32)
      - "The Big Picture: A Show About Allegheny County," informational packet, September 18, 1991 (Box 941, Folder 33)
      - Medical Malpractice Reform, 1986 (Box 942, Folder 1)